Okay, so you think Chiara
can betray Mikoy?
She will never do that.
Her dream is to be free.
Agent Alex, you were a witness.
You saw how she left everything behind.
Family and name.
What I'm holding on to
is that she loves me.
And that's what she chose.
What you are asking from me
is to allow Chiara to reconnect
with the same
criminal organization that raised her,
trained her, protected her,
manipulated her.
How was the meeting last night?
Should we say congratulations
or condolences?
‎All right.
Sweetheart, this is for you.
Chiara, I listened.
Because I said I'd try.
And I know you're thinking
that you can control it.
But it's our job
to think about what if you can't.
What if Chiara is right?
If Viktor, Uncle Vik,
still cares, right?
The risk is too high.
Not because I think you're weak.
Not because I think you're a traitor.
But sometimes, no matter how good you are,
there are just people it's hard
to be objective about, especially family.
It's not personal, but even if
I want to trust you,
we can't base our decision
on feelings alone.
But there's a compromise.
We just need the people upstairs
to approve it.
Angelito. How many girls do you have now?
Oh, none!
What do you mean none? You've got two!
Two? More like three!
Angelito told me they're just friends,
just friendship.
Just let him be.
But on another note, Mr. Mario,
I've noticed vehicles driving around here.
Motorcycles too, like
those riding-in-tandem guys.
Actually even people, watching
this place and circling around.
I have a bad feeling about it.
Actually, Dad, yes.
Some people suddenly
came around doing a census.
And then there's also
a helicopter circling around.
Guys, let's not panic.
But of course, let's be extra careful.
Don't worry, Mr. Mario, I'll handle it.
I'll double our security.
I'll add more people
who look like this guy.
Thank you very much, Captain Pepe.
So what now? Guys, gossipers,
come here.
Come here.
Go find more people who look like you.
All right, Captain Pepe, I'll go look.
All right, hurry up.
He looks like his cousin.
As many as you can,
as long as they look like you.
Is she okay?
Maybe she's stressed?
Trying to release stress?
Oh?
Yes.
Usually, she just sleeps or walks around.
You know, to lower cortisol, apparently.
Maybe she needs a spa day,
something relaxing.
They said Shamrock Spa is good.
You know, actually, this is the first time
I've seen her like this.
So hardworking!
That's how it is.
When things feel messy inside,
it feels good to clean up out here.
It's a stress reliever.
Are you okay?
Actually, no.
I didn't bring my personal pillow.
The pillows here are so soft
that I think I got a stiff neck.
Or maybe it's just tension.
Cause ever since we got here,
everyone seems tired.
Like everyone's carrying
something heavy inside.
You know, I miss it.
When we still had family dinners,
stories, laughter.
Oh, well.
Yes. You're actually really good.
It's so relaxing, it makes me sleepy.
My stiff neck is gone. Amazing!
Now I know why Mikoy
is so in love with you.
You're amazing, all right.
I'm gonna take a nap first.
Wow, you're incredible!
I feel like I just got a massage
from a thousand fairies!
It really feels good.
Are you okay?
Are you planning something?
Mikoy.
I want to talk to Dad.
I need to talk to Dad.
I know the agency doesn't want this,
and I know it's dangerous,
and I know they have a point.
But if I have to tell them
every decision I'm going to make,
how am I supposed to move?
How am I supposed to protect Mom and Dad?
How am I supposed to protect everyone
we want to go back to after this?
And if it's true that
La Morte Bianca is really here…
then I really need to talk to Dad.
The problem with these weapons is,
you can't undo the damage they can cause.
One wrong decision.
One wrong person.
One wrong day.
Sometimes that's enough
to change the world.
To protect everyone's safety,
to make sure no one can use it,
we need to get to them first.
John, Maki!
Let's just switch places.
You do the rounds,
then we'll take the post.
-Copy.
-Where are we?
You, Maki, go over there.
You, John, go over there.
Deaf.
Captain Pepe.
You should do the rounds.
You look tired already.
All right, where are we?
-You go there, and he goes there.
-Okay.
All right, okay.
He's really deaf.
Cook, cook, cook
I'm cooking
Yes, yes, yes
I'm really getting good
At cooking so well
They'll all fall in love
Charmed by a dash of pepper
L-O-V-E, na na na
So delicious, ha ha ha!
I'm gonna eat you up!
Coming right up, coming right up!
Do you want to taste my cooking?
Here it is!
-This is so good, bro!
-Your cooking is so good!
Delicious!
Nice, a special dinner!
Wait, what did you eat?
Wow, why are you
in such a good mood today?
Bro, I had the best sleep of my life
because of your sweetheart.
Now I get why you're in love with her.
Just think about her hands.
They're so deadly!
But also therapeutic
and healing at the same time.
I slept so well when she pressed on me,
my stiff neck disappeared.
Knock, knock, knock, I'm cooking!
Yes, yes, yes, you're really handsome
Oh, me?!
L-O-V-E, na, na, na
I'm cooking
-Yes, yes, yes, you're really amazing
-Yes!
We're handsome if we eat this!
So, what?
Is it final?
The beach?
Then camping!
And content!
-All right.
And exhaustion?
Ouch.
Go ahead and do all that,
so you can really enjoy your vacation.
But be careful, okay?
Yes, Dad.
What a shame, the staff
will be one person short.
Come on. It's fine.
What's important is no one swims too far.
No one goes missing.
And please,
don't fool around inside the boat, okay?
There's more, okay?
Charge your phones, bring water,
let us know… What else?
Text us.
-There.
-Yes.
Okay, text us where you are.
Yes, Dad.
And wear sunscreen.
You really had to slip that in, huh?
Amazing!
-Nice one.
-Let's eat.
-That's enough.
-Come on, let's eat.
-Let's eat, baby.
La-la-la love, la-la-la love
-We cooked this, baby
This tinola is so good
La-la-la love, la-la-la love
Mikoy helped me
Is this witness protection
or a restaurant grand opening?
Oh, Alex.
We deserve the finer things
in life, especially you, right?
Hey, let's go. They're here.
What are you doing here?
Huh?
-We even brought dessert.
-Yup!
Shrimp fritters?
There's effort. There are candles.
There's L-O-V-E.
-Solid!
-Of course!
There's no rat in his head.
Ratatouille.
Come on, let's eat.
-Come on, come on! Sit, sit.
-Try it!
I'll just get a plate.
Sit.
Thanks, Cocoy!
He can handle it.
That looks good.
Sorry, I forgot we have guests.
You know what?
It's perfect because
we're all complete today.
Of course, I want to contribute too.
What am I good at?
Oh, that's something you should all try!
You know, earlier, I had a stiff neck.
I seriously couldn't move.
I was so stressed, so miserable.
Chiara's hands are something else, deadly,
but who would've thought
they also have healing properties
and are relaxing too.
Didn't everything go away?
Because I'm sure,
especially for the agents,
you're even more stressed.
-Eat, massage?
-Sleep!
-All right.
We're getting a massage too, right?
Massage? That would be nice!
It's just perfect.
And Dara and I even brought dessert.
Then straight to sleep, right?
Sounds good.
Here, this is cassava cake.
What happened?
Wow, I slept for so long.
You know that feeling when it's like
I dreamed eight times,
then I astral projected three times.
Look, he's sleeping so deeply!
Especially this one, dead asleep.
Hey!
So noisy, quiet.
-Five more minutes, five more minutes.
-Drooling.
Wow!
You guys sleep like a log!
I already opened all the windows,
and no one still woke up.
Why?
Why is this here?
Wow!
Looks like the idiot's finally relaxed.
I'm almost done anyway.
Do you want one too?
No need, thank you!
With all the knots
in Agent Sianong's muscles,
I'm sure you do too.
You agents are super stressed.
And besides, you're really the one
helping Mikoy and me.
And you know,
it feels good
to know that my hands
aren't only capable of harm.
They can also help people
relax and feel good.
It's okay, thank you!
-Are you sure?
-Yes!
You deserve this.
No, it's okay, thank you!
Perfect, I have a stiff neck.
Really? Where?
Right around here.
-Around here?
-Yes.
Did Chiara put us to sleep?
From what I know,
there are certain pressure points that,
if you press them,
can make you fall asleep.
Maybe that's what happened.
-How?
-Weird.
Wait, where are Mikoy and Chiara?
Hurry, Sianong!
They took my car.
They took my car!
Mikoy and Chiara escaped.
Did the Moraviano get them?
Is there extraction?
Go look for them!
Before the Moraviano get them first!
Before La Morte Bianca catch them!
She changed her way.
Friends!
-Hey, come here. What happened?
-Oh, gosh, the Pinagpalas!
Their house exploded!
Even their bakery is gone!
Why is it only the Pinagpalas?
For sure, it's not an accident.
It's planned!